

## **NGUYEN VAN A**

#### **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

♥ Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and those who resist. Now a pure snore disturbeded sum dust. He ejjnoyes, in or of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

#### **EDUCATION**



#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. m ipsum" (sorrow in itself). Thus, the truncate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Ex and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to copy about your client's business, they will read it. They will comment goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

**ACTIVITIES** Sep 2003 - 2007



#### **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer t distract from the layout. A practice not without controversy, laying out pages wi' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

# HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US am libero tempore, cum soluta nobi

#### **REFERENCES**



#### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

### **SKILLS**





### **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt e almost-not-quite-La and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities